Guide to the Arden B. Schell Watergate Collection, 1972-1974
George Mason University Libraries
- Arden B. Schell Watergate collection, 1972-1974
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (19.1), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    6.90
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (20.1), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    6.91
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (21.1), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    6.92
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (22.1 - 22.4), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    6.93
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (23.1), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    6.94
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (24.1 - 24.2), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    6.95
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 1 (25.1 - 25.3), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    6.96
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2, 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    6.97 (Camp David, Maryland; White House tapes--18.5 minute gap) Ashland Oil, Inc.; Patrick Buchanan; Stephen Bull; Fred J. Buzhardt; Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP) (payment of Watergate defendants); Archibald Cox; Sam Ervin (US Senate); Lewis Fielding; Finance Committee to Re-elect the President; Alexander Haig; Howard E. Hunt; Bruce A. Kehrli; Joseph Kraft; Milk Producers Association; Elliot Richardson; John Sirica; Maurice Stans; Rose Mary Woods; Alan Wright; David Young
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (26.1), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    6.98
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (27.1 - 27.2), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    6.99
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (28.1), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    6.100
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (29.1), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    6.101
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (30.1), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    6.102
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (31.1 - 31.2), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    6.103
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (32.1), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    6.104
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (33.1 - 33.3), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    6.105
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (34.1), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    6.106
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (35.1), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    6.107
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (36.1 - 36.4), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    6.108
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (37.1 - 37.3), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    6.109
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (38.1 - 38.2), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    6.110
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (39.1 - 39.2), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    6.111
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (40.1), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    6.112
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (41.1), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    6.113
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (42.1), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    6.114
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (43.1 - 43.4), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    6.115
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (44.1 - 44.2), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    6.116
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (45.1 - 45.2), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    6.117
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (46.1 - 46.2), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    6.118
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (47.1 - 47.4), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    6.119
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (48.1 - 48.4), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    6.120
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (49.1 - 49.8), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    6.121
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 2 (50.1 - 50.5), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    6.122
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3, 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    7.1 (Key Biscayne, Florida; White House tapes--18.5 minute gap); Spiro Agnew; Robert Bork; Dwight Chapin; Archibald Cox; John Dean; Alexander Haig; Leon Jaworski; Richard Kleindienst; Egil Krogh; William Ruckelshaus; John Sirica; John Stennis (US Senate); Rose Mary Woods; Alan Wright; Ronald Ziegler ("Saturday night massacre")
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (51.1 - 51.5), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    7.2
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (52.1 - 52.4), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    7.3
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (53.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    7.4
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (54.1 - 54.2), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    7.5
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (55.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    7.6
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (56.1 - 56.4), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    7.7
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (57.1 - 57.3), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    7.8
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (58.1 - 58.6), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    7.9
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (59.1 - 59.2), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    7.10
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (60.1 - 60.6), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    7.11
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (61.1 - 61.2), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    7.12
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (62.1 - 62.2), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    7.13
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (63.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    7.14
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (64.1 - 64.7), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    7.15
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (65.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    7.16
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (66.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    7.17
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (67.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    7.18
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (68.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    7.19
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (69.1 - 69.2), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    7.20
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (70.1 - 70.3), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    7.21
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (71.1 - 71.2), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    7.22 (Key Biscayne, Florida)
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (72.1 - 72.2), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    7.23
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (73.1 - 73.2), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    7.24
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (74.1 - 74.4), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    7.25
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (75.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    7.26
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 3 (76.1 - 76.4), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    7.27
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4, 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    7.28 (Executive privilege; White House tapes--18.5 minute gap); Bernard Barker; Charles Colson; Felipe de Diego; John Doar; James O. Estland (US Senate); John Ehrlichman; H.R. Haldeman; Leon Jaworski; Herbert Kalmbach; George Gordon Liddy; Robert Mardian; Eugenio Martinez; Kenneth Parkinson; Peter Rodino; Senate Committee on the Judiciary; James St. Clair; Gordon Strachan; Watergate Hotel
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (77.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    7.29
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (78.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    7.30
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (79.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    7.31
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (80.1 - 80.2), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    7.32
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (81.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    7.33
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (82.1 - 82.5), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    7.34
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (83.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    7.35
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (84.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    7.36
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (85.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    7.37
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (86.1 - 86.2), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    7.38
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (87.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    7.39
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (88.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    7.40
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (89.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    7.41
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (90.1 - 90.2), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    7.42
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (91.1 - 91.2), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    7.43
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (92.1 - 92.2), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    7.44
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (93.1 - 93.2), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    7.45
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (94.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    7.46
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (95.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    7.47
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (96.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    7.48
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (97.1), 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    7.49
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (98.1), 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    7.50
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (99.1 - 99.3), 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    7.51
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (100.1 - 100.2), 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    7.52
  - Evidentiary Notebook 9, Vol. 4 (101.1 - 101.4), 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    7.53
  - Statements of Information / Table of Contents (Books 1-5), 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    7.54
  - Statements of Information, Book 1, Vol. 1, 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    7.55
  - Statements of Information, Book 2, Vol. 1-3, 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    7.56
  - Statements of Information, Book 3, Vol. 1-5, 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    7.57
  - Statements of Information, Book 4, Vol. 1-6, 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    7.58
  - Statements of Information, Book 5, Vol. 1-3, 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    7.59
  - Statements of Information / Table of Contents (Books 6-9), 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    7.60
  - Statements of Information, Book 7, Vol. 1-4, 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    7.61
  - Statements of Information, Book 7, Vol. 5-8, 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    7.62
  - Statements of Information, Book 8, Vol. 1-2, 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    7.63
  - Statements of Information, Book 9, Vol. 1-4, 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    7.64
  - Minority Memorandum on Law and Evidence (Internal Revenue Service), 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    7.65 ("Enemies" list) John Ehrlichman; H.R. Haldeman; Internal Revenue Service (IRS)(misuse by governmental officials); Lawrence F. O'Brien; Randolph Thrower; Johnnie Walters
  - Minority Memorandum on Law and Evidence (Criminal Law Analysis), 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    7.66 (Impeachment; Conspiracy to obstruct justice)
  - Minority Memorandum on Law and Evidence (Introduction / General), 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    7.67 (Impeachment)
  - Minority Memorandum on Law and Evidence (Abuse of Presidential Powers--Introduction), 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    7.68 (Impeachment); Richard M. Nixon (abuse of presidential power)
  - Minority Memorandum on Law and Evidence (Response to Committee Subpoenas), 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    7.69 (Impeachment); Archibald Cox; Senate Select Committee on Presidential Campaign Activities
  - Minority Memorandum on Law and Evidence (Tax Deduction for Gift of Papers--Introduction), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    7.70 Richard M. Nixon (papers); Richard M. Nixon (taxes)
  - Minority Memorandum on Law and Evidence (Kleindienst Confirmation Hearings), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    7.71 (Impeachment); International Telephone and Telegraph (ITT); Richard Kleindienst (confirmation hearings); Richard M. Nixon (abuse of presidential power)
  - Minority Memorandum on Law and Evidence (Government Expenditures at San Clemente and Key Biscayne), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    7.72 (San Clemente, California (government expenditures on)); Richard M. Nixon (papers); Richard M. Nixon (taxes)
  - Supplemental Submission Concerning the Bombing of Cambodia, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    7.73
  - Supplemental Submission Concerning the Bombing of Cambodia, 1, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    7.74 ("Freedom Deal" Operation; "Limdis Ivy Tree" Operation; "Menu" Operation; "Patio" Operation)
  - Supplemental Submission Concerning the Bombing of Cambodia, 2, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    7.75 ("Freedom Deal" Operation; "Limdis Ivy Tree" Operation; "Menu" Operation; "Patio" Operation; Vietnam); US Air Force
  - Supplemental Submission Concerning the Bombing of Cambodia, 3, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    7.76
  - Supplemental Submission Concerning the Bombing of Cambodia, 4, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    7.77 Army of Vietnam: Operations in Cambodia
  - Supplemental Submission Concerning the Bombing of Cambodia, 5, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    7.78
  - Summary of Information (Table of Contents), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    7.79 (Impeachment)
  - Summary of Information (Watergate), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    7.80 (Impeachment)
  - Summary of Information (Organization of the White House and Its Relationship to CRP), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    7.81 ("Political Group" of Advisors); Alexander Butterfield; Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP); H.R. Haldeman
  - Summary of Information (Approval of Political Intelligence Plan), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    7.82 ("Plumbers" Unit; "Political Enemies" Project; "Sandwedge" Operation; electronic surveillance); Democratic National Committee (DNC) (wiretapping of offices); George Gordon Liddy; John N. Mitchell
  - Summary of Information (Implementation of Political Intelligence Plan), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    7.83 ("Gemstone" Operation); Jeb Stuart Magruder
  - Summary of Information (President's Response to the Arrests), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    7.84 (Arrest of Watergate devendents); Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP); George Gordon Liddy; John N. Mitchell
  - Summary of Information (Containment--July 1, 1972 to Election), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    7.85 (Watergate break-in aftermath)
  - Summary of Information (Payments), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    7.86 Charles Colson; Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP) (payment of Watergate defendants); John Dean; Howard E. Hunt; Herbert Kalmbach; Fred Larue; Robert Mardian; John N. Mitchell; Anthony Ulasewicz
  - Summary of Information (Clemency), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    7.87 (Clemency for Watergate defendants); John Ehrlichman; George Gordon Liddy; John N. Mitchell
  - Summary of Information (deception and concealment), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    7.88 Charles Colson; John Dean (obstruction of justice); John Ehrlichman; H.R. Haldeman; Jeb Stuart Magruder; Gordon Strachan
  - Summary of Information (President's Contacts with the Justice Department), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    7.89 John Dean (Testimony); Department of Justice; John Ehrlichman (resignation); H.R. Haldeman (resignation)
  - Summary of Information (April 30, 1973 to the Present), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    7.90 (White House tapes--18.5 minute gap); Alexander Butterfield; John Dean; John Ehrlichman (resignation); H.R. Haldeman (resignation); Richard Kleindienst; John Stennis (US Senate); Alan Wright
  - Summary of Information (Appendix A), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    7.91 (UHER 5000 Tape Recorder; White House tapes--18.5 minute gap); John Sirica
  - Summary of Information (Appendix B), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    7.92 Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP); House Banking and Currency Committee; Wright Patman (US Representative); Peter Rodino
  - Summary of Information (Abuse of Power), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    7.93 (Huston Plan; Impeachment; "Plumbers" Unit; wiretapping); Richard M. Nixon (abuse of presidential power)
  - Summary of Information (Illegal Intelligence-Gathering), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    7.94 (wiretapping)
  - Summary of Information (Special Investigations Unit), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    7.95 (Pentagon papers; "Plumbers" Unit); Leonard Boudin; Central Intelligence Agency (CIA); Daniel Ellsberg; Lewis Fielding; Howard E. Hunt; Egil Krogh; George Gordon Liddy; David Young
  - Summary of Information (Concealment of Evidence), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    7.96 (Pentagon papers; "Plumbers" Unit; wiretapping); William Matthew Byrne, Jr.; Central Intelligence Agency (CIA); Daniel Ellsberg; Patrick Gray; Alexander Haig; Morton Halperin; Richard Helms; J. Edgar Hoover; George Gordon Liddy; Time Magazine
  - Summary of Information (Misuse of Internal Revenue Service), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    7.97 Internal Revenue Service (IRS)(misuse by governmental officials); George McGovern (supporters and IRS investigation); Lawrence F. O'Brien (income tax returns); George Wallace (IRS investigation of)
  - Summary of Information (Kleindienst-ITT), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    7.98 Jack Anderson; Grinnel Corporation; International Telephone and Telegraph (ITT); Richard Kleindienst
  - Summary of Information (Agriculture Department), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    7.99 (Milk--Price supports for) Department of Agriculture
  - Summary of Information (President's Properties), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    7.100 (Key Biscayne, Florida; San Clemente, California); General Services Administration (GSA); Richard M. Nixon (improvements made to properties)
  - Summary of Information (Conclusion), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    7.101 (Impeachment); Richard M. Nixon (abuse of presidential power)
  - Summary of Information (Refusal to Comply), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    7.102 (Impeachment); Richard M. Nixon (refusal to comply with House Judiciary Committee Subpoena)
  - Summary of Information (Willful Tax Evasion), 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    7.103 Richard M. Nixon (pre-presidential papers); Richard M. Nixon (taxes)
  - Transcript: meeting between the president and John Dean, February 28, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    8.1 (Transcripts of White House tapes)
  - Transcript: meeting between the president, John Dean, and H.R. Haldeman, March 13, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    8.2 (Transcripts of White House tapes)
  - Transcript: president's cassette recording of his recollections, March 21, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    8.3
  - Transcript: meeting between the president, John Dean, and H.R. Haldeman, March 21, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    8.4 (Transcripts of White House tapes)
  - Transcript: meeting between the president, John Dean, John Ehrlichman, and H.R. Haldeman, March 21, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    8.5 (Transcripts of White House tapes)
  - Transcript: meeting between the president, John Dean, John Ehrlichman, H.R. Haldeman, and John Mitchell, March 22, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    8.6 (Transcripts of White House tapes)
  - Transcript: telephone conversation between the president and John Connally, March 23, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    8.7 (Transcripts of White House tapes)
  - Transcript: meeting between the president, John Ehrlichman, and Egil "Bud" Krogh, July 24, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    8.8 (Transcripts of White House tapes)
  - Transcript: meeting between the president and leaders of dairy industry in the cabinet room, March 23, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    8.9 (Transcripts of White House tapes)
  - Transcript: meeting between the president, John Connally, George Schultz, Clifford Hardin, John Ehrichman, John Whitaker, Phil Campbell, and Donald Rice, March 23, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    8.10 (Transcripts of White House tapes)
  - Transcript: meeting between the president and John Dean, April 16, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    8.11 (Transcripts of White House tapes)
  - Transcript: meeting between the president and John Dean in the president's EOB office, April 16, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    8.12 (Transcripts of White House tapes)
  - Transcript: telephone conversation between the president and Richard Kleindienst, April 19, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    8.13 (Transcripts of White House tapes)
  - Transcript: meeting between the president, John Ehrilichman, and George Schultz, April 19, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    8.14 (Transcripts of White House tapes)
  - Transcript: meeting between the president and John Mitchell, April 21, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    8.15 (Transcripts of White House tapes)
  - Transcript: meeting between the president and Alexander Haig and a meeting between the president and Ron Ziegler, June 4, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    8.16 (Transcripts of White House tapes)
  - Transcript: recording by the president of his recollections of a telephone conversation with John Mitchell, June 20, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    8.17 (Transcripts of White House tapes)
  - Comparison of passages from "Eight Recorded Presidential Conversations", 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    8.18 (Transcripts of White House tapes)
  - The September 15th White House conversation: Cause for the Impeachment of Nixon and Investigation of the Department of Justice, 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    8.19 (Transcripts of White House tapes)
  - Transcript: Miscellaneous, 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    8.20 (Transcripts of White House tapes)
  - Special Prosecution Force Status Report, June 26, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    9.1
  - Letter from Amos E. Heacock to the Honorable Judge John J. Sirica, April 7, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    9.2 (Assassinations) Alex Bottos; Central Intelligence Agency (CIA); Amos E. Heacock; KGB; John Sirica; Watergate Hotel
  - Letters: Fulbright to Nixon and Nixon to Fulbright, June 25, 1974 and July 12, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    9.3 (wiretapping); William J. Fulbright; Henry Kissinger
  - Statement of the Honorable Paul S. Sarbanes, House Judiciary Committee, July 25, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    9.4 Paul Sarbanes (US Representative)
  - John Ehrlichman Testimony, People v. Ehrlichman, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    9.5 John Ehrlichman (Testimony)
  - Opening Statement of Charles W. Colson, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    9.6 Charles Colson
  - Statement of Egil Krogh on the Offense and His Role, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    9.7 Egil Krogh
  - Draft remarks / Honorable Don Edwards, July 24, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    9.8 Donald Edwards (US Representative)
  - Statement by Congressman Don Edwards of California, July 24, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    9.9 Donald Edwards (US Representative)
  - Roll Call Sheet, 93rd Congress, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    9.10 House Committee on the Judiciary (roll sheets)
  - The Impeachment Inquiry: Its Meaning, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    9.11 (Impeachment)
  - Impeachment (Miscellaneous), 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    9.12 (Impeachment)
  - Resolution Offered by Mr. Donohue, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    9.13 (Impeachment)
  - Articles Offered by Mr. Mezvinsky and Mr. Hungate, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    9.14 (Impeachment)
  - Article II, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    9.15 (Impeachment)
  - Impeachment Inquiry, Background Materials, 93rd Congress, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    9.16 (Impeachment)
  - Principles of Presidential Responsibility for Criminal Acts of His Subordinates, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    9.17 (Impeachment)
  - Impeachment Inquiry Statements, etc., 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    9.18 (Impeachment)
  - Judicial Procedures for National Security Electronic Surveillance, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    9.19 (wiretapping)
  - Constitutional Grounds for Presidential Impeachment, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    9.20 (Impeachment)
  - Presidential Statements on the Watergate Break-In and Its Investigation, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    9.21
  - Syllabus, Supreme Court of the United States: United States v. Nixon et al., 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    10.1 (US v. Nixon)
  - Schell, Arden (notes, 1 of 4), 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    10.2 House Committee on the Judiciary
  - Schell, Arden (notes, 2 of 4), 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    10.3
  - Schell, Arden (notes, 3 of 4), 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    10.4 House Committee on the Judiciary
  - Schell, Arden (notes, 4 of 4), 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    10.5 House Committee on the Judiciary
  - Impeachment Inquiry--press statements, 93rd Congress, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    10.6 (Impeachment)
  - Impeachment Inquiry--clippings of congressional records, newspapers, etc., 93rd Congress, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    10.7 (Impeachment--Newsclippings)
  - Newspaper clippings--Watergate, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    10.8 (Watergate newsclippings)